Quoc - Huy Vo



huyvq1428@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/huy-vw



https://vo.guochuy.tech

Summary

Experienced Back End and DevOps Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the product company. Skilled in Software Development, Cloud Computing, Computer Networking, and Machine Learning. Strong engineering professional with a Computer Network and Communication focused in Data Communication and Computer Networking from the University of Information Technology.

Experience



M DevOps Engineer

Meete.co

Sep 2020 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

- Build CICD system (deploy python application, build & deploy java, golang, nodejs application)
- Write and manage CI, orchestration job files
- Build cloud server network system (both GCP and AWS)
- Reconstructed microservice system (Docker, Hashicorp stack)
- Managed cloud server system (GCP and AWS, CI, BI tool, gateway)

Back End Engineer

Meete.co

Jul 2019 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

- Designed requirement documents from business problems
- Designed ERD (Entity Relationship Diagram)
- Designed Database (SQL PostGresql & MariaDB, noSQL MongoDB)
- Designed & Developed APIs (java, python, golang)
- Migrated Database to server system
- Designed & Developed a new back-end framework (golang using DDD parttern)
- Cross review code team member
- Researched Block-chain solution for Loyalty

Education



University of Information Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Network and Data Communication, Computer **Network and Communication**

2016 - 2021

Courses projects:

- Developed sudoku application and build load balancing server system for sudoku application
- Build IDS/IPS network system
- Designed and developed wifi marketing system (both embedded firmware and Pfsense server)
- Configured Cisco network devices
- Build rain cover IoT system using sensor, voice, and cloud server remote control

Scientific research program:

- Build a system to detect Malicious Web Resources through Machine Learning
- Build a system to detect CNAME Cloaking-based Tracking through Machine Learning

Student club: NetClub (Networking Club)

- Organized network troubleshoot contest (2018)
- Organized network seminars with companies
- Organized technical sharing

Licenses & Certifications



Cisco Certified Network Associate Routing and Switching (CCNA) - Cisco

Networking Academy

Skills

Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) • Software Development • Cloud Computing • Computer Networking • Machine Learning • Linux • Python (Programming Language) • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Google Cloud Platform (GCP) • PostgreSQL

Honors & Awards



Scientific research program - University of Information Technology

Oct 2019

Build a system to detect CNAME Cloaking-based Tracking through Machine Learning - VND5 million



Scientific research program - University of Information Technology

Oct 2020

Build a system to detect Malicious Web Resources through Machine Learning - VND5 million